嗨，大家！在干什么?
Hey,you guys.
Hey,what are you doing?
-筹备婚礼
-有趣得很,我们也正合计这事呢
- Figuring out our wedding plans.
- Funny. We were doing the same thing.
疯了,场地,服装,食品
It's really crazy.
The hall,the dress,the food.
-没想到结个婚这么贵
-是很贵
- I had no idea how expensive this was.
- Yeah,it is really pricey.
-第一次算出结婚费用，我被那个数字吓呆了
-结果你们怎么做的?
- I freaked when I heard the numbers.
- So,what did you two do about it?
简单,我各个项目都想出了一些省钱的方案
It was simple. I came up with
some cost-cutting solutions..
结果莫妮卡叫我去死
wrote out a list,
and Monica told me to go to hell.
没钱好省的,接受事实,这的确很费钱
There's no way around it. Just accept
that this is gonna cost a lot of money.
听说每年花在结婚上的钱高达400亿
I heard that weddings are,like,
a $40 billion-a-year industry.
这其中我贡献过半
Yeah. And I'm responsible
for just,like,half of that.
我不知道,一天花这么多钱太过了
I don't know. It's a lot of money
to spend on one day.
嘿,我以前结过婚
我都没有盛大的婚礼
Hey,I've been married before,
I don't need a big wedding.
我所想知道的是你没有迷上我弟弟并和他上床
All I ask is that you don't do ecstasy
and make out with my brother.
我觉得这钱应该用在更有意义的事上
But really,it does seem like
this money could be put to better use.
嘿,你可以买一吨安利的产品
Hey,you could buy a ton
of Amway products.
-或者全部捐给慈善机构
-喔,这个想法不错
- Or give it all to charity.
- Oh,that's great.
那些安利的东西该怎么样卸货呢?
How am I gonna unload
all those Amway products?
当真?
Are you serious?
把婚礼经费捐献给慈善事业
Yeah. How would you feel if we gave
all the wedding money to charity..
我们就到市政厅登个记。如何?
and we just got married at City Hall?
这让我越发想娶你了!
I think it would make me
wanna marry you even more.
我必须要说，真是个高姿态
I gotta say,you guys,
that's an incredible gesture.
下次你结婚也这么干如何?
Maybe you do that
next time you get married.
下次我要在夏威夷斜阳下结婚
No,no,no. The next time's
gonna be Hawaii at sunset.
下下次吧
But maybe the time after that.
家访
The.One.With.The.Home.Study
-嘿！ 忙啥呢？
-嘿！
- Hey. What's going on?
- Hey.
领养中心有人来家访，所以我们在扫除
Our adoption social worker is coming,
so we're cleaning the apartment.
我们？
"We"?
你说不想我掺和，怎么又责怪我不干活
You know you don't want me to help.
You can't have it both ways.
你们能否领养全靠这个人说了算？
Is this the person who decides
whether or not you get a baby?
－差不多，这人来视察我们的生活环境
－我们必须表现得完美
- She's coming to see where we live.
- And it has to go perfectly.
若她有丝毫不满，我们就永远没戏
If she doesn't like us,she can keep
us off every adoption list in the state.
我可以过来友情协力一把
她没准爱看肥皂剧
Hey,maybe I should stop by.
She could be a soap opera fan.
小人物认识演艺名流，可以加分呢
It's very impressive when
the little people know a celebrity.
小人物？
"Little people"?
名流
"Celebrity."
差不多满分了
So I think I'm just about done here.
除非你还有什么，像黄书，香烟？
Unless you have any bad stuff hidden
somewhere,like porn or cigarettes?
什么？
What?
－才没有！
－钱德
- No.
- Chandler.
你无中生有，污人清白
I don't,and I'm offended
by the insinuation.
沙发下没有杂志？
So there's not a magazine
under the couch..
厕所水箱后没有一包香烟？
or cigarettes taped to the back
of the toilet tank..
录像机里没有下流影片?
or a filthy video in the VCR?
香烟和杂志我认帐，但带子不是我的！
I'll admit to the cigarettes and magazine.
But that tape is not mine.
-也不是我的！
-永远不会知道是谁的了！
- It isn't mine.
- I guess we'll never know whose it is.
可以帮忙吗？
May I help you?
我们来捐钱给孩子
Yes. We're here to make a rather
sizable donation to the children.
捐钱不论多少，心意都是一样重
我们都会感激
Any contribution,large or small,
is appreciated.
数目这样大，你一定会异常感激
I think you're gonna appreciate
the crap out of this one.
-你们真大方
-我们不留名．匿名捐助
- Well,this is very generous.
- And we don't want any recognition.
完全匿名
This is completely anonymous.
完全匿名，两个陌生好人
Completely anonymous.
From two kind strangers.
X先生和菲比布菲
Mr. X and Phoebe Buffay.
我们可以把二位的名字登到新闻通讯里
We can put your names
in our newsletter.
－没必要
－布菲的拼法是：Buffay
- Not necessary.
- Buffay is spelled B-U-F-F-A-Y.
X先生的写法是：麦克.哈纳根
And X is spelled "Mike Hannigan."
也许标题应该写:
迷人的夫妇让世界变的更好
Possible headline:
Attractive Couple Makes World Better.
我代表孩子们多谢两位
Well,on behalf of the children,
thank you both very much.
-感觉真棒
- 是啊，非常棒。
- I'm glad we did this. It feels so good.
- It does. It feels really good.
还有免费T恤拿
Oh,look. And we get these free T-shirts.
那是我健身穿的
Actually,that's the shirt
I wore to the gym.
难怪是湿的
It's moist.
-艾玛会很快起床的
-哦，好的。
- Hi. Emma will be up in a minute.
- Oh,good.
嘿，罗斯
听说你跟查莉的事了,替你难过
Hey,Ross,listen. I heard about
you and Charlie. I'm really sorry.
没事,美貌的考古学家多的是!
That's okay. I'm sure there are tons of
other beautiful paleontologists out there.
-当然!
-只有一个!就是她!
- Absolutely.
- There was one. She's it.
其他的就好象是桥洞居民一样!
All the rest look like
they should live under a bridge.
今天想怎么玩?
So,what are you gonna do today?
带艾玛去街心游乐场怎么样?
I was thinking of taking Emma
to the playground.
上帝啊，什么?
Oh,my God. What?
我又没说带她去武器弹药博物馆
Like I said,I was thinking of taking
Emma to the Museum of Knives and Fire.
我反对艾玛去游乐场
Okay,look,Ross. I do not want
Emma going to the playground.
因为?
Because..?
好吧，如果你想知道…
All right,if you must know,
I had a traumatic..
我小时候荡秋千遇险
swing incident when I was little.
-真的?
-我才四岁
- Seriously?
- Yes. I was 4 years old.
我荡秋千
And I was on the swing..
突然头发缠到铁链
and then all of a sudden my hair
got tangled in the chain.
结果妈妈剪掉我一大缕头发,才救我出来
And to get me out,my mom had
to cut a big chunk of my hair.
结果有好几星期头发都不整齐
And it was uneven for weeks.
你竟熬了过来?
And you made it through that?
简直可以拍成电影
I wonder who's gonna play you
in the movie.
你尽管拿我取笑,反正我就是不想艾玛去
Okay,fine,you can make fun of me.
I do not want Emma going there.
而且我在想克莱尔・丹尼斯（电视电影演员）
And I was thinking Claire Danes.
你的悲剧令我同情
Look,I'm sorry to hear
about your tragedy.
不过秋千很安全
而且艾玛喜欢荡秋千
But the swings are perfectly safe.
And besides,Emma loves them.
-我们同去,你就知道了
-秋千速度40英里/小时
- You should come,and you'll see.
- Those things go,like,40 miles an hour.
荡到高处
And there's that moment
when you're at the top..
鬼才知道会不会返回地球
when you just don't know
if you're gonna return back to Earth.
宇宙充满小孩子绕轨道运行
Space is filled with orbiting children.
来嘛
Look,please,just come on.
你若看见艾玛的小表情,决不会后悔
When you see the look on Emma's face,
I swear,you won't regret it.
-好吧
-太好了。
- All right.
- Good.
你不会像有的妈妈那样
把自己愚昧的恐惧遗传给小孩吧
You don't wanna be a mom who passes
her irrational fears to her children.
愚昧?
"Irrational," huh?
下次你被家里的蜘蛛吓到
我们再谈这个话题
I'll remember that next time you freak
out about a spider in your apartment.
这两个可以相提并论吗!我保证那上面有30种毒液
That's the same. I'm sure there are 30
different species of poisonous swings.
哦，天哪，领养中心的来早了
Oh,my God.
The adoption lady is early.
好的好的.镇静镇静!!!
Okay. Okay. Here we go.
Here we go.
站直咯
Stand up straight.
微笑
Big smile.
你好,请问这是"毛骨悚然"家吗?
Hello. Is this the Creepy residence?
还以为是领养中心的来了
你来得正好
We're waiting for the adoption lady.
But I'm glad you're here.
今早打扫时发现的,不知道你用不用得上
I was cleaning this morning
and I found this.
我不知道你是不是想用,但是...
I don't know
if you wanna use it,but..
你真好
Oh,this is so sweet of you.
不过我不需要头纱,我根本不需要服装
But I won't be needing a veil.
I actually won't be wearing a dress at all.
裸体婚礼,我不会参加的!
I told you,I am not coming
to a naked wedding!
我们不会开招待会
No. We're not having a big reception.
我们把婚礼经费捐给儿童慈善事业了
We took the wedding money
and donated it to a children's charity.
你疯啦?
That's crazy!
-是慷慨！
-疯得这么慷慨
- Generous.
- Crazy generous.
抱歉,只是无法想象.
一生只有一次啊
I'm sorry. I can't imagine giving up
my one wedding day like that.
我们不同! 我不在乎什么盛大婚礼
Well,we're different.
I don't care about having a huge party.
头纱是很美,但是
This is really nice for you,but..
你看我一戴上,简直就…
Oh,please. I put this on
and I just look like..
美极了
Well,radiant.
管它的!我不需要头纱婚纱这些玩意
All right,but who cares? I don't need
a pretty veil and a fancy dress.
对! 你们是互许终身
That's right.
You're making a commitment.
不管在广场举行还是别的什么地方都是一样
You know,that's the same
whether you do it at the Plaza or..
-你选了啥地方?
-市政厅
- Where you gonna do it?
- City Hall.
好地方
Oh,that sounds nice.
市政厅的人该忙不过来了
I was just there for jury duty.
They've really spruced that place up.
没关系,这是我自己的决定
Okay. It's okay. It's okay. It's okay.
I've made my decision.
但我真正想要的,只是一个盛大的婚礼
What I really want
is a great big wedding.
-但钱已经捐啦
-可以要回来
- But you gave all the money to charity.
- Well,I'll just ask for it back.
-不行吧
-怎么不行?
- I don't think you can do that.
- Why not?
她结婚!这可比什么
愚蠢的小孩子重要多了!
This is her wedding day. That's way
more important than some stupid kids.
说得好,省着点,等领养中心的人
来了再表演不好吗
That's sweet,honey,but save
something for the adoption lady.
-好，准备就绪
-好
- All right,okay. Be careful.
- Okay.
小心,小心她头发
Careful. Watch her hair.
Watch her hair!
-她才三根毛!
-我知道，我知道
- Rach,she's got,like,three hairs.
- I know. I know.
但是很漂亮
糟糕,扯掉一根
But they're just so beautiful.
Oh,my God,I just pulled one out.
我保证，她很安全,你看她多喜欢玩秋千
I promise you she's safe.
Watch how much she loves this.
- 好吧好吧
- 你准备好了吗,亲爱的?开始喽
- Okay. Okay.
- Are you ready,sweetie? Here we go.
小心
Okay,careful. Okay.
她笑了
She's smiling.
她真的很喜欢
Look at that,she does like it.
看,我告诉过你的吧
See,I told you.
哦,天啊,看看她,真有不怕死的精神.
Oh,my God. Look at her,
she's a little daredevil.
-让我推好不好?
-哦，当然。
- Oh,God. Let me push. Can I push?
- Oh,absolutely.
你拿相机,在尿布包里
Oh,God. Okay,get the camera.
It's in the diaper bag.
好。
Okay.
还怕秋千,真够傻吧?
See? Scared of the swings.
I bet you feel pretty silly.
-我们真要把钱要回来?
-结婚要用!
- We're asking for the money back?
- It's for our wedding day.
他喜欢男的还是女的?
我们中的一个要去跟他调情
Now,is this guy gay or straight?
Because one of us has to start flirting.
同一天捐两次钱
You here to make another
donation the same day?
前所未有呢
I don't think that's ever
happened before.
是个同性恋,你上
Gay. Go.
你衣裳真帅
Oh,my God,I love your shirt.
今天捐的钱,我们想要回
The donation we made earlier?
Well,we want it back.
啊?
Excuse me?
那是办婚礼的钱,我们本想从简
Okay,that money was for a big wedding
we thought we didn't want.
但现在我们改变了主意
But it turns out we do.
要我们退还你们捐给孩子们的钱?
So you're asking us to refund
your donation to the children?
对!
Yeah.
感觉不错
This feels really good.
对不起,但婚礼对我相当重要
I'm sorry. I am. But this wedding's
just really important to me.
关我啥事
这也许是好事
Hey,it's none of my business.
Besides,this is probably a good thing.
别把孩子惯坏了
让他们吃饱穿暖怎么行
We've really been spoiling the children,
what with all the food and warm clothing.
这么说不公平,结婚是大事
That's not fair.
A person's wedding is important.
尤其对我!
And especially to me.
我没参加过毕业典礼,没有毕业舞会
I didn't have a graduation party.
And I didn't go to prom.
在我的甜蜜16岁,
And I spent my sweet 16
being chased around a tire yard..
我被精神病人狂追
他还说
by an escaped mental patient who,
in his own words,wanted to:
"杀"我什么的
"Kill me,or whatever."
我应当有个隆重的婚礼!
So I deserve a real celebration.
你这个流汗男,别想让我内疚!
And I'm not gonna let some sweaty
little man make me feel badly about it.
她可能没有在说我们
She could've been talking about
either one of us.
好的,来吧
Okay. Here we go.
祝好运
Good luck.
你在舌吻？
Tongue,really?
我叫劳拉,我来做领养家访
Hi,I'm Laura. I'm here
for your adoption interview.
我叫莫妮卡,他叫钱德
Hi,I'm Monica.
And this is Chandler.
- 请进！
- 谢谢
- Please come in.
- Thank you.
-请进.喝点什么?
-喝水可以了
- Would you like something to drink?
- Water would be fine.
你总算来了
We're so glad that you're here.
我们好兴奋，要开始领养小孩了
We're excited about
getting this process started.
我们爱小孩,爱得要死
Because we love kids.
Love them to death.
不是要孩子"死",只是修辞手法
Well,not actually to death.
That's just a figure of speech.
我们爱孩子,不多不少
We love kids the appropriate amount..
符合法律法规
as allowed by law.
-你们家好可爱
-谢谢
- Your place is just lovely.
- Thank you.
这里有家的温暖
Yes,this building does have
a wholesome,family feel to it.
我好象来过,这里还有谁申请领养?
I feel like I've been here before. Any
other couples in the building adopting?
一楼那家? 我们应该比他们先要孩子
Is that that couple on the first floor?
We should get a baby before them.
他还想卖毒品给我
That guy tried to sell me drugs.
其他都是好人
But other than that,
wholesome,wholesome building.
- 怎么？
-我想起来了,难怪来过
- What?
- I realized why I remember this place.
-怎么?
- 哦，没什么！
- Really? What is it?
- Oh,it's nothing.
我和一个男人约会,结果无疾而终
I went on a date with a guy who lived
in this building. It didn't end very well.
那人该不是叫乔伊崔比亚尼吧?
That wouldn't,by any chance,
be Joey Tribbiani?
-就是他!
-当然是他
- Yes!
- Of course it was.
我们有过一个很棒的晚上，过后,他说他再打电话给我
结果再没联络!
We had a great night. In the morning,
he promised he'd call and he didn't.
这混球!
Rat bastard!
-你们该不是他朋友吧?
-当然不是!不!
- So you're not friends with him?
- Oh,God,no.
-当然不是!不!
-当然不是！
- No,no,no.
- No. Nope.
抱歉提这事
Well,I'm sorry I brought it up.
那么你们当中有人打算待在家里吗？
So are either one of you planning
on staying at home?
有人吗? 名人驾到
Hello? Anybody in there
order a celebrity?
什么人?
What was that?
走廊上的疯子
That's just some crazy guy
who roams the halls here.
不过他对小孩很慈祥
He's great with kids,though.
- 罗斯，噢，天啊， 你还好吗?
-他娘的!
- Ross. Oh,my God,are you okay?
- Son of a bitch!
别紧张，我又没说F打头那个字（fuck）!
Oh,relax. I didn't say the F-word.
罗斯，看,早告诉你了,秋千危险
Ross,see,I told you!
Those swings are evil!
算了,这辈子再也不许艾玛接近它
That's the last time Emma is getting on
one of those things for her entire life.
别这样,不是秋千的错,是我错
No,no,no. Okay,it wasn't
the swing's fault. It was my fault.
还有他的错
And kind of that kid's fault.
他还笑,算你狠
Who is still laughing. Nice.
在再有人受伤之前，我们走吧
Come on. Can we just get out of here
before somebody else gets hurt?
这样吧,你去荡秋千,你就会…
No. Wait. I have an idea.
I want you to get on the swing..
发现那有多安全
and you'll see that there's
nothing to be afraid of.
我明白了
I know what this is all about.
你一贯嫉妒我的头发
You've always been jealous of my hair.
这才是成年人的做法
克服愚蠢的恐惧
I just think you're an adult,okay?
And you should get over your silly fears.
-好!我要做
- 好！
- All right,fine. I'll do it.
- Good.
-如果你敢抓蜘蛛
-在哪儿?
- If you hold a spider.
- Where?! Where?!
我说"如果"你敢抓蜘蛛
If you hold a spider.
听见了
I know.
没事吧?是我,乔…
Guys,is everything okay?
It's me,Joey.
领养!
Adoption!
到底什么事?
What's going on?
就是那个疯子名叫
Oh,it's just like I said,that crazy..
伯特的，在走廊上跑
Bert,roaming the halls.
- 嗨！伯特,接着跑
- Guys?
- Keep on roaming,Bert!
今天我们不看你疯了
We don't want any crazy today!
他独自一个在外面，不会出事吧?
Is he all right out there by himself?
没事,他哥哥照顾他
Oh,yeah. He has a caretaker.
His older brother..
叫厄尼
Ernie.
- 伯特 和 厄尼? (芝麻街的动画角色)?
-绝对不是编造的
- Bert and Ernie?
- You can't make this stuff up.
- 怎么了？
- 我们等会再说，一切都好！
- What's going on?
- We'll talk later! Everything's fine!
听起来一切都不好！
Everything doesn't sound fine.
伯特 和 厄尼 有一只大黄鸟！
Bert and Ernie have a big yellow bird.
你没说过你16岁时被男人追杀的故事
You never told me about that guy
and your sweet 16.
-真可怜
-结局还算好
- I'm sorry about that.
- Oh,it ended okay.
我朋友毙了他
One of my friends shot him.
至少你会有个体面婚礼,你该得的
At least you'll get a proper wedding.
You really deserve that.
没错,我这辈子还没风光过
Yeah,I really do. You know,
I had nothing growing up.
就像被我剥夺金钱的那些孩子一样
Just like the kids
I took the money from.
看出你的意思了,别又想让我退回去
No. No,no. I see where this is going.
Don't make me go back there.
抱歉,但我又想把钱给孩子们了
I'm sorry,but I want to regive the money
to the children.
但是我们不能,我是说
你管那男人叫流汗男
But we can't. I mean,
you called that guy a sweaty little man.
除非你在说我
我们从没真正弄干净过
Unless you were talking about me.
We never really cleared that up.
我不能用这钱办婚事,这不道德
Look,I can't have a wedding
with this money now. It's tainted.
好吧,退回去吧
Fine,we'll give the money back.
如果慈善捐助处那家伙又叫咱们难堪
If that guy at the charity
gives us a hard time..
我朋友好久没开过枪了
my friend hasn't shot anyone
in a really long time.
我想说,你们的家庭抚养小孩似乎很理想
I must say this seems like a lovely
environment to raise a child in.
你尽可以在各种家具下面搜查
You are welcome to look
under any of the furniture..
绝无黄书和香烟什么的!
because,believe me,you won't find
any porn or cigarettes under there.
在到处看看之前,要问你们一些问题
Before we look around,let me make sure
I have everything I need up to here.
带你看看婴儿房
Why don't I show you the baby's room.
-你干什么?
-你不让我进来
- What are you doing?
- You wouldn't let me in.
-我以为你们出事了
-才没有!
- I thought you were in trouble.
- Well,we're not.
但你叫我"伯特",
But you called me "Bert."
那是"危险"的暗号
That's our code word for danger.
-我们没约定过什么暗号
-是吗？
- We don't have a code word.
- We don't?
应该约一个
We really should.
从今往后，"伯特"就用来作为
遇到危险的暗号
From now on,"Bert"
will be our code word for danger.
参观完婴儿房
So that was the baby's room.
-下面参观哪里？
-除了沙发下面都可以参观！
- What room should we see next?
- Any room that isn't behind this couch.
有些人不懂他的笑话
但我觉得他真幽默
Some people don't get him,
but I think he's really funny.
我不在乎被你粗暴对待
I did not care for that.
你得回避
You have to leave.
你和这个社工睡过，再没联络她
You slept with our social worker
and never called her back.
她还在生你的气，不能让她见你
She is still pissed,
so she can't see you.
好，好，好！
Okay,okay.
- 怎么了？
-忘了拿球棒
- What?
- I forgot my bat.
天啊！
Oh,my God.
最后警告，我们不想和你做朋友！
And for the last time,
we do not want to be friends with you!
也不想买你的球棒！
And we don't wanna buy your bat!
你在这儿干什么？
What are you doing here?
伯特，伯特，伯特，伯特
Bert. Bert. Bert. Bert.
-你们是朋友？
-我来解释
- Are you friends with him?
- I can explain.
乔伊你说
Joey?
好吧！
All right. Okay.
你有种，还敢回来
You have got some nerve
coming back here.
-你竟不打电话给我
-什么？
- I can't believe you never called me.
- Excuse me?
你连我名字也忘了，我叫乔伊
You probably don't even remember
my name. It's Joey,by the way.
不必说你的名字，我记得，女士
And don't bother telling me yours,
because I totally remember it,lady.
我一直等你电话
I waited weeks for you to call me.
我给你电话号码，你没联络我
I gave you my number.
You never called me.
还想栽赃给我
Don't try to turn this around on me.
我可不是让你
I am not some kind of social work..
想做就做的
that you can just..
＂社工＂
do.
-我确信给过你电话
-真的？你想想看
- I'm pretty sure I gave you my number.
- Really? Think about it. Come on.
你漂亮，聪明，有趣
You're a beautiful woman.
Smart,funny.
咱们相处甚欢
We had a really good time.
如果我有你电话，怎么可能不打给你？
If I had your number,
why wouldn't I call you?
不知道
I don't know.
可能我搞错了，对不起
Well,maybe I'm wrong. I'm sorry.
现在道歉太晚啦
你伤了我的心
Hey,too late for apologies. Okay?
You broke my heart.
就为了忘掉你，我睡了多少女人啊！
You know how many women
I had to sleep with to get over you?
-乔伊，等等
-不！
- Joey,wait..
- No!
我等得够久，不可能再等了
I waited a long time!
I can't wait anymore.
抱歉让你们笑话了，真尴尬
I'm sorry that you had to see that.
I'm so embarrassed.
-没事，
-我们理解
- Oh,that's really okay.
- Yeah. We totally understand.
-约会可够人受的
-你们真好
- Dating is hard.
- Boy,you people are nice.
我得说…
And I've got to say..
你们一定会是很棒的父母
I think you're going to make
excellent parents.
劳拉！
Laura!
我们回来啦
We're back.
还想要钱？
Are you here to take more money?
你们应该找提款机
Because I think what you're
looking for is an ATM.
不不,我们把钱退给你们
No,no,we're here
to give the money back.
为了孩子
Yeah. Because you know what?
It's all about the children.
至于我们的婚礼
Although it's also about the wedding.
好吧,给.不要!喔天啊!
All right,here. No. Oh,God.
好像忘了道喜，恭喜你们
If I haven't said so already,
sir,congratulations.
哦,等等
Oh,wait. Wait.
如果我们捐一半留一半呢?
What if we give half to the charity
and we keep half?
或者,就象我们留75%,而另外25%...
或者,90%和10%
Or,no,like,75 percent for us
and 25 percent for.. Or,no,like,90-10.
好啦!你知道吗?已经够了,好吗?
Okay,you know what? Enough,all right?
我要插手,而且做决定
I'm stepping in
and putting my foot down.
作为你的
未来老公，我要说了算
As your future husband,
I'm gonna make this decision for us.
你说咋办？
What do you think we should do?
-不是你们说了算了
- 什么？
- It's not your decision anymore.
- What?
代表纽约儿童，我拒收你们的捐款
On behalf of the children of New York,
I reject your money.
-但是我们在给你钱啊
-退给你们
- But we're giving you this.
- And I'm giving it back to you.
当作赞助好了
Come on. Consider it a contribution.
你真大方
Well,this is very generous.
支票拿走，祝你们婚礼成功，幸福甜蜜
Take the check. Have a great wedding
and a wonderful life together.
听来不错，我们以后存了钱
Sounds good to me. We can save up,
come back in a few years..
过两年捐更多
and make an even bigger donation.
好得很，下次记得找布莱恩
And when you do,ask for Brian.
-布莱恩是你?
-不！
- Oh,is that you?
- No.
喂？
Hello?
哦，嗨！
Oh,hi.
喂，天啊，真的，我等不及要告诉钱德
Oh,my God,really?
I can't wait to tell Chandler.
好，再见！
Okay. Goodbye.
－打错电话的？
－是劳拉
- Wrong number?
- That was Laura.
她替我们大大美言
我们正式上了领养排队名单
She gave us a great report and
we're officially on the waiting list.
－太好了！
－下个电话
- That's great.
- Now we just wait for a call..
就会有人说有宝宝等我们去领养了
and someone tells us
there's a baby waiting for us.
喂?
Hello?
看见乔伊的球棒了吗？
Have you seen Joey's bat?
好了， 我捉到了蜘蛛！
Okay. I got a spider.
有两只，我挑了大的一只。
There were two,
I picked the bigger one.
-好的
- Okay.
感觉一切正常。
This feels perfectly normal.
好了，你上秋千去
Okay,get on the swing.
好啊
Okay.
好
好啊！
Okay.
-看到了吗?
-啊，没事了，我可以玩秋千了。
- See?
- All right. I can do this.
是啊。干得好！
There you go. Good for you.
知道吗？
我习惯小蜘蛛啦。
You know what?
I'm getting used to this little guy.
-完全没有异样的感觉。
-因为它爬上你脖子啦
- I don't even feel him in here anymore.
- That's because he's on your neck.